{
    "question": "Narrative text yang bagus dan jarang di dengar orang??",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "The story snow white<br>In earlier times there lived a , who named Snow White . He lived with his aunt and uncle because his parents died . One day she heard her uncle and aunt talking about leaving Snow White in the castle because they wanted to go to America and they did not have enough money to take Snow White with them . princess Snow White did not want her uncle and aunt to do this . So he decided to escape .<br><br><span>\u00a0The next day he ran away from home when her aunt and uncle were having breakfast , he fled into the wood . In the wood she felt very tired and hungry . Then she saw this cottage . She knocked but no one answered her so she went inside and felt asleep Meanwhile seven dwarfs came home from his work . They get into . There, they found Snow White woke up from his sleep . He saw the dwarfs . The dwarf said : \" What is your name ? &#039; Snow White said , \" My name is Snow White . \" One dwarf said , \" If you want , you can stay here with us . &#039; Snow White tells all about her story . Then daughter snow and the seven dwarves are now living happily ever after .</span>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "aku-dapt-tugas-dari-guru-binggris-ku-disusruh-membuat-cerita-sp-750",
            "question": "aku dapt tugas dari guru b.inggris ku disusruh membuat cerita \"spoof\" dari pngalaman pribadi, tapi aku bingung gimana crtanya. tlg bantu ya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "kamu pasti punya kan pengalaman lucu ,,, kamu tulis aja bhs indonesianya nntik saya coba nerjemahin<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-spoof-pake-twist-falling-into-a-well-dong-306",
            "question": "Contoh text SPOOF pake twist \"falling into a well\" dong :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSpoof text: Falling Into a Well</span>\n<span>\n</span>\n\nThere was a man. When he was walking, he fell into a well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nMany people saw the incident so they came to save him. Unfortunately no \none could enter the well to bring him out. Later, a smart man came up \nwith a bright idea to throw the man a strong rope to try to pull him out\n the well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nWhen the rope reached\u00a0 and hit the man\u2019s head, he shouted angrily: \u201cDon&#039; bother me! Pick your own well, I am bathing.\u201d\n<br>\n\nDo you get the point why that short passage can be labeled as a spoof \ntext? Before we are going to go further, Let&#039;s see its rough translation\n to help you to\u00a0 get better understanding\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "combine-the-sentences-using-too-so-or-either-and-neither-1-d-745",
            "question": "Combine the sentences using : Too, so, or either and neither    1. Dogs\u00a0can't eat vegetables. Cats can't eat vegetables\r\n2. We haven't eaten yet. Father hasn't yet\r\n3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not seventeen years old\r\n\r\nJawabannya yang Jelas ya :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1. Dogs can&#039;t eat vegetables. Neither can cats<br>2. We haven&#039;t eaten yet. Father hasn&#039;t either<br>3. Mitha is not seventeen years old. I am not either<br><br>setau aku begitu aja sih udah betul. mudah-mudahan membantu ya:)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-dari-dialog-bergaining-987",
            "question": "Contoh dari dialog bergaining?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "In a traditional market there are two friends named Rifky and Obet. They are looking for goldfish, they are going to make a party at Rifky\u2019s house by roasting goldfish.<br><span>Rifky:\u00a0we should buy cheaper goldfish because our money is not much<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0sure, that\u2019s why we have to round to get the cheaper price<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0but I\u2019m tired..we have rounded the whole part of this market but the price of all goldfish is almost the same<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0Look at there\u2026! There\u2019s a goldfish Fishmonger that we have not been there yet<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0ok, come on<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0what the price of this goldfish in a kilo?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0It\u2019s 27.000 rupiahs a kilo<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0That\u2019s too expensive,\u00a0\u00a0may I bargain?</span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0How much can you pay, boys?<br></span><span>Obet: what about 20.000 rupiahs a kilo?<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0sorry I can\u2019t. it\u2019s a local goldfish, taken from ponds around this area<br></span><span>Rifky:\u00a0\u00a0give me a break\u2026you must decrease the price. You said that we may bargain.<br></span><span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I&#039;ll make a special price for you, boys.</span>\u00a025.000 rupiahs a kilo. What about that?<br></span><span>Obet:\u00a0I don\u2019t think so, give me 22.000 rupiahs a kilo and we\u2019ll take 3 kilos<br></span><span>Fishmonger:\u00a0I\u2019m loss..I have no profit if I sell with that price. Just for you boys I give you 22.500 rupiahs per kilo but you have to buy 4 kilos. Do you agree?<br></span><span>Rifky:give us for second please.<br></span>RIFKY WISPERING OBET<br><span>Rifky: \u00a0 it\u2019s cheaper among all the goldfish Fishmonger that we have visited. Should we take it?<br></span><span>Obet: yes I know\u2026ok we just take it<br></span><span>Rifky: Ok, we\u2019ll take 4 kilos for 22.500 rupiahs<br></span><span>Fishmonger: that\u2019s a wise buyer\u2026here\u2019s the fish boy. I hope you feel satisfied.<br></span><span>Rifky and Obet: thank you</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-see-his-to-if-go-doesnt-at-house-aldi-will-her-school-see-co-389",
            "question": "1.\u00a0see-his-to-if-go-doesn't-at-house-aldi-will-her-school-see-cousin-he-her-to    2. and-holiday-bali-if-have-will-his-lombok-long-go-year-Mr.Kukuh-family-to-they-and-this-a\r\nkalo disusun jadi conditional sentence ini jadinya apa ya?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "no.2 Mr kukuh and his family will go to bali and lombok if they have a long holiday this year",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-past-tense-menggunakan-used-to-712",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat past tense menggunakan used to",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "that scissors used my mom<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "contohnya : i used to studying at night<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-buatkan-teks-bahasa-inggris-tentang-pengalaman-yang-terd-803",
            "question": "Tolong buatkan teks bahasa inggris (tentang pengalaman) yang terdapat Simple Past Tense dan Simple Perfect Tense!!",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<strong>NEW YEARS HOLIDAY<br></strong>When my holiday at home alone, do not go anywhere, when New Years, i was my large family grilled chicken. Very happy family get together, but this year&#039;s holiday was not very pleasent, for some reason??but with family better from with my friend, at the same moment, i stay at home or help my mom. This holiday very boring, calm only, not go play, my mom a sick, this holiday only talk my mom.<strong><br></strong>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Last week, me and my friends went on a road trip to Bali. We rented a jeep, and travel around, through mountains until beaches. We went to\u00a0Mount Agung, it\u00a0would be cold and foggy, but we&#039;ll also see the beauty of the island from up there. Next, we went down and reach a beach called the Pink Beach. By there, we go on boats to see smaller islands, which was fun. We traveled around Bali for 2 weeks, and it was fun.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-yang-membuatmu-suka-dengan-cerita-malin-kundang-apa-saja-yg-d-727",
            "question": "Apa yang membuatmu suka dengan cerita malin kundang    apa saja yg dapat diambil (pelajaran) dari cerita tersebut?? (minimal 2)\r\n\r\njawabnya pakai bahasa inggris y.. \r\nplease....",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "tidak boleh membantah kedua orang tua ..<br>maaf gk bisa bhs. inggris !!<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "1. bercerita realiti dan fakta<br>2. bisa dijadikan pelajaran buat kita<br><br>hikmhanx kita tidak boleh melawan ortu terutama ibu kita,, karena dia yg mengandung kita selama 9 bulan",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buat-text-hartatory-explenation-yang-berjudul-effect-of-insomni-716",
            "question": "Buat text hartatory explenation \u00a0yang berjudul effect of insomnia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Effect of Insomnia<br>Horatory -&gt; thesis -&gt; reason -&gt; suggestion<br><br>Insomnia is kind of illness that makes people hard to sleep. Due to its negative effect, this illness is categorized as the dangerous symptoms. The reason could be classified from Internal feelings of the person. Therefore if we have this illness, better to have consultation toward the doctor. We stand to benefit by the greater time of sleep that we have.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "boleh-minta-contoh-soal-dari-ungkapan-maksud-532",
            "question": "Boleh minta contoh soal dari ungkapan maksud?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Maksud -&gt; Idea or opinion<br><br>I think the best way to be expert in mathematics is by practicing everyday.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}